<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zain Imran</title>
    <link>http://www.zainimran.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zain Imran</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.zainimran.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gender Imbalance in Tech</title>
      <link>http://www.zainimran.com/blog/gender-imbalance-in-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.zainimran.com/blog/gender-imbalance-in-tech/</guid>
      <description>As a student of Computer Science who his aware of his male privileges, I am deeply saddened over the sidelining of women in Computer Science industry and academia. This exclusivity starts at an early stage in a woman’s life, when she is conditioned to take more interest in socially acceptable ‘girlish’ stuff instead of encouraging her curiosity about computers and electronics. If a girl does venture into such interests by mistake, she is quickly reprimanded and reminded of her stereotypical role in society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.zainimran.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.zainimran.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Zain Imran and I am currently a Computer Science student at Lahore University of Management Sciences. I love front-end web development and hence, I am always on the lookout for interesting projects.
This blog is built with Hugo, and deployed using Netlify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://www.zainimran.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.zainimran.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>Profile Experienced cultural representative. Strong operations professional with a BS focused in Computer Science from LUMS. A perfectionist who outputs incredible results for any task and responsibility he undertakes.
Experience Senior Project, Lahore University of Management Sciences July 2017 - present
 Social Media Profiling Tool based on public data scrapped from social networks  Teacher Assistant, Lahore University of Management Sciences September 2017 - present
 Did teaching assistantship for CS 200- Introduction to Programming  Certified Smile Maker, Project Smiles June 2017 - August 2017</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>